tuberip.com 2015-05-12

# Www.tuberip.com - Privacy Statement

Privacy Policy

Tuberip respects your privacy and does not collect any personal information that is not submitted by the user (such as submitting a site suggestion, premium sections, or sending a page to a friend).

1\. Collection of Data An Internet User's browser sets Cookies (when enabled) that contain small amounts of data on the Internet User's computer after a visit to any web site. Cookies assist Tuberip.com in tracking Internet Users' activities beginning from a Publisher's web site or subscription e-mail through an Advertiser's web site that the Internet User links to from the Publisher's site or e-mail. If the Internet User re-visits the Advertiser's site directly, Tuberip.com is able to continue to track the Internet User's activities on the Advertiser's site and reward the Publisher that referred the Internet User. The Cookies themselves tell Tuberip.com nothing about the Internet User personally. No information is obtained from the Internet User or Internet User's computer to generate the unique identifying number of the Internet User. Tuberip.com's servers automatically generate the unique number. None of Tuberip.com's Cookies are used to perform "User Profiling". Tuberip.com does receive and record partial e-mail addresses of Internet Users, only in circumstances where the Internet User has voluntarily provided its identity and contact information through the Advertiser's Web site or Publisher's Web site. This partial e-mail address does not enable Tuberip.com to personally identify an Internet User.

2\. Use of Personal Information and Disclaimer. By the use of the Site or its services, the Member, visitor or User expressly agrees that the Site may use any information that it gathers or collects about the Member, visitor or User including personal information that has been provided by the Member, visitor or User for technical, administration, research and development, customer administration, age verification, marketing, promotional and advertising use and for the transmission of email communications, the sending of products or the fulfilling of any terms and conditions; and furthermore that the Site may disclose or provide such personal information to its affiliates, agents and service providers that provide goods and services, for purposes of providing such goods and services.

The Site is not responsible or liable for the use of any information that a Member, visitor or User may provide, or that is gathered by third-party websites that have banner ads or links on the Site. This Site does not control, monitor or endorse the information gathering practices or Privacy Policies of any of those third-party websites, and those third-party websites may have different privacy policies than this Site. Whenever applicable, each Member, visitor or User should seek to read the Privacy Policy of any third-party website provider that has an advertising banner, advertises or has a link on the Site.

All Members, visitors and Users of this Site should consider any information provided to or collected by the Site as non-confidential, and consequently the Site assumes no liability or responsibility if any information relating to any Member, visitor or User is intercepted and/or used by an unintended recipient.

By your acts of signing up as a subscriber to the Site, accepting the Terms and Conditions of the Site and affirmatively consenting to accept emails from this Site, you are agreeing to all of the following: (1) that Site has your permission to collect your email address and all personal information you supply relating to that email address; (2) that Site has your permission to disclose and transfer your email address and all other personal information you supply to its affiliates, agents or service providers that provide goods and services in accordance with the Terms and Conditions of TubeRip.com.

3\. “Opt-Out” – Revocation of Consent Procedure. The Site also offers all Members and Users a procedure for “Opting-Out” if the Member or User subsequently chooses to revoke or withdraw any consent to receive Offers by sending an e-mail to support@tuberip.com clearly stating that the Member or User has revoked or withdrawn consent to receive any future Offers.

4\. Security Measures Tuberip.com employs industry standard security measures to ensure the security of all data. Access to Tuberip.com customer data is accessible via password protection through the Advertiser and Publisher Accounts created by each Advertiser and Publisher, and to designated Tuberip.com employees who require system level access in order to perform their jobs. Access to Internet User data that identifies the Internet User's name and/or e-mail addresses is limited to designated Tuberip.com employees who require such access in order to perform their jobs and to an Advertiser or Publisher that provided such information. Each Advertiser and Publisher is responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of its own password used for accessing its accounts on the Tuberip.com Network.

5\. Policy Changes Tuberip.com may find it necessary or be legally obligated to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any changes will be posted at this site. Except as otherwise required by law, modifications to this Privacy Policy will not affect the privacy of data collected by Tuberip.com prior to the effective date of the policy change. Effective March 01, 2010
